So why I'm asking, so it's called backtesting. So what is backtesting? So let's say you have a data set. OK, so let's say you have an array of. Can you see my screen?
yes sir
ok so let's assume
that
let's say you are
importing
Y finances
YF
import
numpy as
NP
import
fund
I think it will be
let us see if it wonders or not
so then you use data is equal to
YF dot then you use the ticker
ticker means let us say you just use Apple ok
the stock ID that is there in the stock exchange
sorry and then you use the period and then you use so how do you know about this okay
so when is when there is when without using google so you can go here and you can just
do this and it will come on the right hand side okay the function can you see the screen
so that's how you know so you need tickers that is which tickers you're going to do
in the start and end which may be none and you can also use uh period and interval so period means
for how many uh days let's say so you can say six months so you can see an ex there are the examples
below okay here there are examples so i think six months and um interval is let's say one day
okay
so you will run it
so it's running
so the more you run it
so this is called documentation
so those who are learning to code
and trying to learn
essentially you are using chat gpt okay
but there are two phases of learning guys
okay
one is understanding that you can actually code
if you are given the resources without using like For example this is how I use chat GPT okay I do not ask it so i do not ask it to so how this is how i learn coding myself for new things i do not ask it to give me
uh the answer i just ask it to uh let's say give me the optimum thing okay uh that helps me
understand so similarly you can also do that too okay so you can ask strategy pity and it will
help you out in that fashion so now this is the data set so if you see data it will be coming out
like this okay so what i will do is that i will change this into an edit so you can see the first
so data dot so let's say columns
I am saving the column names as this
column names are saved now I see it's
pandas are ok so what is the difference this is the data frame
it's usually
it's a data frame and
you actually work with it in using
pandas. Now the difference between
pandas and numpy is the following.
Numpy is a raw array
raw matrices
or tensors, one dimensional array
or two dimensional arrays or three dimensional arrays
or multi dimensional arrays.
But pandas
are two dimensional and
the thing is
that you can actually access it by
the names of the
columns or rows okay which you cannot do it in numpy because there's no name for example if you
just change it into uh data underscore array is np dot array of data let's see yeah
and you just show data you will see now
you will see now it a raw now data set Okay The columns has disappeared The column names The good thing is that if you work with the column names using Pandas
that's okay to do, but that may actually
you may need to do a lot of different things. For example, in this
case, it's a multi-index. So, you have to reset the
index every single time and that's sometimes hard. Okay. That sometimes
takes you away from the whole stuff. So I will be using
just this raw data of matrices,
matrix and that will help you. So this is the data set.
So if you want to just visualize it, just do this. You just do this
as df is equal to data
okay. So now I will introduce the pandas. So just
import pandas as pd
and just what if you want to visualize just do this
data frame of this data underscore array
and you can just do columns
as columns and if you just visualize this
you will see that our data set only so see the
date and time were removed but the column names are there
even if you do not want to give the columns
it will look like this
ok so this is
so now you have to access by 01
but this is just to visualize it
so this is the same matrix as the numpy array
but it is a better visualization
a tabular format you can access it by the names
of this ok this is the only difference
all of you understood
this guys
yes sir
ok
Yes, sir.
nothing but a multi-dimensional so if you remember that just remembering I
that why I like to give in a mathematical format a data set is nothing but x is equal to x1 x2 dot dot dot dot xn or t is the data set we have right
And you can see below what's coming.
and I hope all of you can see properly and each of xi is in r to the power d.
In this case, in this case, I hope it is d is equal to 5, right?
okay in the case of a B is equal to 5 and what is the trading strategy a
trading strategy is nothing but a let's say you tell it talk about
trading strategy at a time T because at time T minus 1 the strategy will be
different mathematically right because the moving crossover may be different so
a trading strategy is a function of time so T at time T is a function of this X
Right. Which is going from therefore.
It's a D T cross D therefore. Right.
The T time points of D dimension T is in columns just like this.
It's taking in this entire data set. The T is in columns. D is in rows.
Sorry. I mean, T is the number of rows and D is the number of columns.
and this is going to
this set.
Like,
buy, sell, or hold.
Right?
This set it is going.
So, this is just a trading strategy.
Because, at the t-th time point, we are deciding
based on some mathematical functions.
Like, if the moving cross over
Now, there is another thing.
This function also has something called theta.
That we don't know.
So, this theta is unknown right.
so this theta is
unknown right
so that's why
we need bath testing
okay let's do some
That's why we need backtesting.
Guys, can you see this zoom out thing?
Can you see this?
All of you?
Is it visible, this text?
Yes, sir.
All of you, it's visible?
yes
ok
so
that's why we need backtesting
so what does backtesting do
it does nothing but
it divides this
so essentially it's based on past data
right it's actually training
we are building
We are finding theta based on not on t, because if we take in xt, it does not make sense, right?
Because xt is the right time point based on this.
xt minus 1.
The theta is found based on that.
Okay.
Okay, theta is found based on that.
We are finding based on the xt minus 1.
And, yes.
So, we are finding based on xt minus 1 and then we are testing on xt.
or not testing we are taking decisions on Xt based on Xt So it involves X all of them all all t values but this is how the decision happens okay so this is a small subtle aspect out there now
one important thing is that we sometimes
yeah so what what all of you guys done here is based on xt minus 1 so that's a
practicing is important because it helps you in segregating this aspect okay so
in segregating this so when you are actually sharing the data you actually
sharing on this result on this XT this one but actually you should share your
data on XT what it has happened on XT okay I mean it can also happen that you
can divide till x like till d minus 1 and you can also do it till this you can also do it like
x underscore d c dots you can do also like do it as this
make sense so you can also do it like first d data points and take decisions and then
share your findings
based on
this.
Yeah, so your findings
or your results on
helps you
to find best theta.
Okay.
But you should share your findings
on the data set you are tasting.
Make sense, guys?
See you soon.
And mathematics of financial data, right?
But today we'll be talking about
stochasticness of prices.
So let's do some live coding.
So let's say download
import Yfinance as YF.
Import Numbuy as NP.
Import Pandas as PD.
So, once we import them, let's get some price.
So, we get data.
And then we do yf.download.
Then we have the ticker price.
Let's say Apple.
Ticker.
So what is AAPL It Apple Apple stock I thought it was AAPL It was thicker
And then there's a period.
Let's say you take a period of six months.
And then you take...
So, you can know more about a function.
If you forget, what will you do?
You can just do YF download.
and then you do a question mark and if you do it you will see on right hand side you will get to
know about the function so for example ticker the tickers it can be an array too so it tickers you
can see you can see it's a list and then it's a there's a period it can be valid period is
six months one year many things can be there and there's the interval
go to the parameters directly
so this is called a doc string
so
and then there is an interval
an interval
let's say
one day
so we download it
we have to use a
apl serve
Oh sorry
That's why I bought here
So once it download
Once it
Once you download it
Then you have to
So let's see
How it looks like
So what we will do is
We will do data.head
It looks like this
Now the thing is
This is a multi index frame
okay so we want to it's very hard to work in this so we will it's nothing but
a matrix right so what we will do is the following we will just convert this into
a proper numpy array a two-dimensional array okay so we will use something
called price 2d and we will do it NP dot array and this data
OK. And then we can visualize what this price today looks like.
It looks like this It boring Right So sometimes people want to do is they use Panda So visualize it You can directly use Panda here But as you can see it not easy actually it not easy to deal with it so to visualize it what you do is you do pd dot data frame
price 2d the issue is that you there is no heading to it okay you can see the heading is gone so
you can actually use
I think data.columns doesn't work.
Oh, it works.
So,
I'll
or to t t
just give me a minute
Okay.
So you can see, let's make a new data frame called columns.
Just a list with this list.
close I
you can make low
open
and volume
what you can do is that when you do make this refram you can just add columns
equal to columns again you can
understand this function if you don't know understand this function from and now you can see
this close high column coming close high low
open volume column coming you can just do head to just to
see the top okay but we want to work with this price
because that's what we want.
So, now we will work with
the probability distribution, how it came.
So, we will close this.
Let's close this.
okay so now what so we have the price to you just to remind you so if you look at
price to reshape you will see it's 125 cross 5 that means there are five
features so what we will do we will just take the first one that is the clues I
think it's close the first one is close yes so let's just take the first one
so we will just take price is equal to first column so the door colon and then
first column sorry the second column so so now if you look at price it looks
like this an array a one-dimensional array so now what we can do is the
following let's investigate this price of it so we can just plot this so for
that we need to download this import matplotlib so observe that let's
plot this PLT dot now let's plot this price it's one dimension you will see
this is also into do PLT dot show so you will see this naturally came up right
125 days of data now we can do we can this is an array and we can do an
histogram of it so what we can do is field hist price and density is equal to true
If you do this you will get this density So what does it mean It means it kind of a continuous distribution like this Now what you can do another thing is you can divide this into
price, let's say, underscore cat,
categorically, we'll say, or let's call it discrete. You can make it
like this, np.where.
So, essentially, you're going to replace, so
let's calculate the average.
So let's say
what I'm saying is that
now if price 2D
or just price, if it's
greater than
let's say
mean of price
or NP dot mean
then it's high
else it's low.
So, I am discretizing the price.
So, if you look at this, it now looks like this.
So, it's basically like probability kind of thing.
What's the probability?
Higher probability or lower?
I don't know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, this is what it looks like.
Now, how to plot this?
And to plot this, so here it was continuous.
So, we plotted a continuous version of it.
Now, we will plot a discrete version.
For that, so for continuous, we plot histogram and for discrete, we plot bar plot.
So, what we will do?
We will first count it.
So, we will do values, comma.
So, essentially, we need what?
We need number of unique values of high and number of unique values of low.
So, what we will do?
We will do, we will use something called np.unique.
Okay.
So, you don't know this.
So, what you do as a student?
You don't know this.
I am telling you.
So what you do is just run this and see what it gives.
This is how you learn.
So what I do is that I usually get this.
I get to understand which function to use from ChatGPT and then I learn on this one.
Because in research, you will be creating or doing something that is...
So in the future, we will learn, of course.
We will learn very fast using ChatGPT.
But a time will come, let's say after five years, six years, where people will learn very fast.
and then
chargeability
training
requires a lot
of data
right
so
then what
will happen
when you
when new
data are
coming in
it's like
it's not
training itself
right away right so it will be like delayed by 2 years of knowledge which you need to learn quickly So that where you learn in this new way OK that why you learn in this
The process of learning should be the same so that you can learn new knowledge.
This is how you learn to code.
This is how you everyone learn to code when there was no Google.
There was something called documentation.
This is a documentation.
OK, so there is a NumPy documentation.
So if you just sign NumPy documentation, you will see this.
and you will see lot of
guides are there, like a lot of guide.
And it's like every function has some meaning.
So, fundamentals, every function has some meaning.
But it's hard to understand. That's why I use GPD
to learn that what function should be used
and then use, go to documentation or search here, like use that function,
press and understand it. So how to understand a function? You see parameters
here. That's why whenever you write a new something, something code from scratch,
always write parameters, input and output. There is a returns and there is parameter.
You can see. So how is it written?
I will show you. Does it take an argument in a way?
Parameters is input, arguments
and returns is what is the output of the function.
I'm just used to hearing arguments
huh?
yeah they're right parameters
it's the same thing
yeah tomorrow it will be a different name
so
yeah
I mean you can see this right
arguments but it's also called parameters
uh
am I doing something
yeah so you can say that
np.unique takes in an array like structure
okay and then there is a thing called access
access tells you that in which if it's a multi-dimensional
array then which dimension you want me to take the average of or uniqueness
of or is it the entire thing okay
So that's where it makes sense.
That's where it's, that's where the, yeah, that's where the whole thing happens.
So when you do NP so that why access is also important But here we want to do np in the entire price so we do in price underscore discrete which you already defined above and okay so there other things so
we want the count of it right we want understand what we want for a blur plot we need the counts
yeah and the corresponding values like values and the counts like your high and
low and their corresponding counts right as a pair so and does it give counts
just see
Actually, return the sorted array, okay.
Yeah, so there is something called return counts.
If it is true, it is the number of times each unique, okay, so we need that.
So, what is the outputs?
outputs is okay values unique values unique values and the counts yeah you
You can see an example here probably.
Yeah, values, counts here.
Okay.
So you can just.
So now here it's price underscore discrete.
So now if you have done this, now if you look at values.
and counts, I don't know, yeah.
You can see it's high, low, and it's showing to a 45 high and 80 low.
But we want mean of that.
So what we do is that the values are the same,
but we change counts as counts divided by,
what do we want?
What do we want?
Counts divided by?
I think it's 2, but I'm not sure.
No, it will be average of it.
You want...
The sum of the terms.
So, counts will be now average.
So, if you look at counts now,
they are average.
Now, the sum of them is 1 now,
because now it's a probability distribution.
Now, we will do bar plot.
values,
comma,
counts
and
plb.show.
Now,
you can see
it's a
probability
distribution.
Okay?
Make sense,
guys?
Make sense?
All of you, can you give a thumbs up?
Okay, great.
So now let me show some notes I have written for you for, okay, another thing is left.
Quite a few things are left.
But yeah, so this is now, the whole idea is this, that, okay, so no, we are not done yet.
We have some things left. So that means if you aggregate all the XIs, that is becoming a random variable.
But is each XI a random variable? So what we will do is that if you remember price has shaped 125.
OK, it's a 125 vectors. So what we'll do is 125 is 25 to 5. Right.
so
what we will do is that
we want to change this
I want to change this in
so I want to
plot together
the price of
5 days
for
1 to 5 then 6 to 10
then 11 to 15 like this
together so what do we need
to do for that we need to change
like change this 1 to 5
5,
6 to 10,
10 to 11 to 15,
all these things,
this 5,
5,
5 arithmetic progression,
I want to cut it and attach in the columns Right So how to do that This is a very Python to do that we do using reshape so what we will do is we will write price
now 2d not 2d it's a price new as price dot reshape now when you reshape it
imagine now it's 125 cross 1 or 125 vector now we want to reshape it into 5
length the time is 5 and 25 is the number of columns so 5 rows and 25
columns so 5 comma 25 now you can see price underscore new it looks okay let's
now look at it in a data in a data frame format so pg.dataFrame so that you
can visualize it this is how it looks like each is a time series of 5 length
each is a stock of see can you feel just say price if you look at the difference
Just give me a minute.
Thank you.
okay so it has distributed in a different format it has distributed in
yeah
lengthwise you can see that
okay it is distributed in lengthwise
But that really fine no worries so just give me a minute
Just give me a minute.
okay so yeah so it will be the same thing there's something called order for
trans style so we will use that here so we will use order is equal to so now I
I didn't read this so therefore what we'll do is we will look at the reshape
okay so NP dot reshape will read about it yes so yes you can see there is an
order which I didn't read. So, C is the one where it reads
in the index order. F is the one
to read
yeah
correct. So, yeah. So, it's a four-trap. So, let's
see.
Yeah. Now, you can see the 1, 2, 3,
You can see the 1, 2, 3, 4 are the same here.
Got it guys?
Yes, Sharaf.
Why did you choose F specifically over C or A Oh why did I choose
Yes.
So, because I want to plot 1 to 5, then 6 to 10, then 11 to 15, like this, in a single way.
I want each of them in single columns.
If I don't have this, it was giving me, see, it was expanding this.
see it was like there is a string
I want to do the string like this
ok
into a column but they are doing the string
row wise
oh so it is just a different format
yeah yeah
that was I was doing this
so now what we will do is
we will plot this now
so we will do plt
plot
this price name
So, now you see that every time, okay, so one thing I missed.
So, I need to change this price new.
So, I want each one of them from 1 and I am telling you why.
So, price new divided by price new
of the first row. So, you can see all of them
are 1 now. Okay, there is a reason behind that.
yeah so you can see that all of them won because i want to see that
from every fifth day onwards how do the because i believe that after five days let's assume that
five days have no effect on one another so you can see after every five day like
what I am saying is that
even if it started from the same value
this shows
the path of a 5 day price movement
ok
which tells you that
which tells you
that today's
price is just one of the options
of one of such paths
because we are only measuring
relative distance right
because that's how we gain money
We do not gain money by absolute distance.
money by relative distance because we are dividing with a number because how we because with a let's
say there's a stock price price so we buy the number of shares of it okay so let's say i have
the stock price is 100 i buy i use thousand dollars so i buy 10 shares of it so if tomorrow
if the stock price becomes 110 i'm actually gaining profit of 10 per 10 stock so i get 100
I get because of the difference, not the absolute values.
So therefore, if I do it with respect to 1, all of them are combined to the same initial value.
Now I see the price change actual that can give us money.
So this price change that you see, some 5 slates.
So what I'm saying is that each price path is just one of the options.
So how do we model this?
So if you remember that it means we model this as X1, X2, X3, X4, right?
what I'm saying is x, y, each of the x, y's is one of the options
among its, yes Raghav
so I understand what you're saying about how the graph is showing the multiple options
that any day could go over the next 5 days, any stop could go over the next 5 days
but how does the price underscore new equal price underscore new
divided by price underscore new zero show what you're
describing? What I'm saying is that
we want to change the,
we want to only see the change, right?
So, if I, I mean, if I do not do this,
it will be, you will be looking something at this,
because every price has different starting point.
So, we are not actually, if we plot this,
we are not changing, looking at,
not X1, because this is relative,
which price change is relative to the starting point.
so to see the stochasticness in it the variability in it
we have to actually combine them to the same point
and then see the variability so that's what I am doing here when I am combining
all the prices relative to the first day's price
that means I am bringing all of them to day one and then seeing
then like I am seeing the flowering of the stock market
for each different days
am I making sense Raghav?
yeah so I get what you doing but I not fully I don fully understand how the code does what you are doing so how does it work okay so when i doing this i mean i dividing by price new so price
new is nothing but the first row oh right
so price knew nothing but the first row
so when I am writing this essentially I am saying that
divide each row by the first row
like so in python we write codes in factorized format
when I say a by b in python
in between two numbers is usually divided by two numbers.
But if I have an array, divided by two arrays,
that means each element of the array is correspondingly divided by the same index element in the other array.
Yes, Raghav.
Right, so what you're doing is you're taking the first row
and you're dividing each subsequent row by that first row
to see how much it ranges from the first row.
Okay, thank you.
Yeah, so that we normalize it to the first row and then we see the change of the movement.
We are essentially measuring how the price is changing with respect to the first day.
As if the first day is the same.
And so you can see the stochasticness here.
And now what we'll do is we'll plot each one of these histograms.
So we'll do it as price underscore new of zero.
density is equal to
so if you plot this
you can see this for one
for the next one let's see
oh sorry this will actually I have not divided it yet
so if you see one it will be a single bar
so it doesn't make sense because the first one is all one
now it looks like this
so you can see that every time point is kind of a different distribution
ok
so what I am saying is that each of the XI is the probability distribution in itself And if exponential can have increased stochastic process
So it's like if you take the log scale of it, the distributions are kind of similar, you can say.
but you can see here that
if it kind of increases, so that's the whole idea
so what I am saying is that
the main takeaway point is the following, so I have written some notes for you
so each xi
each xi is a random variable
okay
and
so each
exercise is a
random variable
so now how
would you measure
randomness
we measure
randomness by
probability
distribution
so in
discrete values
we take
we use
something called
bar plot
which is
nothing but
each exercise
takes values
like high
and low
which I am
saying a1
a2.am
with probability
is p1
p2.pm
where each
of these
is greater
than or equal
to 0
and sum
is 1
like we
have seen
here
okay
and
here for this case
for continuous values probability distribution
is nothing but a histogram
so each take a real number
each x i takes real numbers with
probability distribution of f x where f x is
greater than or equal to 0 and integration of that
so integration is nothing but the area under the curve
okay and say
and you can think connected by a
continuous curve let's say
Are we using Riemann's integral?
Yes, Riemann's integral.
And the Riemann integral is 1.
In general, you can use Riemann integral, actually,
but let's not go into the details of it.
And just here, fx is not a probability,
because you can see, if it's a probability,
then it cannot take the value of 12, right?
So what does it mean?
What does fx actually mean?
So fx doesn't mean anything alone,
but what it means that fx dx is the probability of x taking values in the interval x between x and x plus dx interval.
For example you can see that here 12 is not the probability but at 1 12 times 0 That is if you calculate the area under the curve that will be 12 times 0 means 0 That is the meaning of the probability So similarly here fx times dx the length
of that and the height actually calculates the probability of x taking values in the
interval x, x plus dx. And humans cannot really understand always randomness. So, often we
understand the distribution by its mean, median,
range, variance, skewness,
cartesis,
percentiles,
like this,
this values.
I don't know what that term means, I was just wondering.
It's okay, yeah.
So, variance, so mean, okay,
yeah, I should have mentioned this, so
mean is the average, median
is also kind of the, like,
These are the data, like,
ways to measure the data, not the variance,
they're kurtowskis.
yeah I'm just going I should have mentioned that so
range is the difference between maximum and minimum variance is again the variability
skewness tells you that it's how
skewed it is toward the left or the right for example
if you look
at the performance
of any student okay let's say an average student like me
If you take any performance, my performance is not symmetric around the number.
Okay.
My performance is always skewed towards lower value and sometimes I perform well.
So it's left skewed.
Similarly, a really good performer is right skewed.
Who is always on the, like a good student is always on the higher average or higher score.
and sometimes a student can do lower scores.
So that's what skewness measures.
You can read the mathematics online.
I'm not going into that because that will just not use good use of time.
And then kurtosis is how much it's picked at certain point.
How much it's picked.
Like the more the pick it is, that means the more dense it is.
So you can say kind of skewness,
variance is nothing but proportional to square of it.
power of it so for example
just give me a minute
Yes, I have written this answer a long time ago when I was a school student.
So, I think it's five years ago.
so you can see I have written like what
what does moment means
for example a Taylor series expands a function in terms of
you know square you know x square x cube similarly
so for example all these coefficients tell you the how much
x square is inside that function similarly the first moment tells you the location
and center of the distribution
standard deviation tells you how much spread of variability is there
skewness tells you how much it is right skewed or left skewed
curtis tells you the peakedness of it
so the more the flat it is
the more negativities, the more positivities, the more peaked it is
so essentially higher moments
tell you more about each of this
so the order of moments tell you about the
symmetricity because if they symmetric
the positive
and negative cuts away symmetric around
zero the positive and negative
cuts away
so that's what order of moments tell you
and
cartesis tells you about yes
so the even order of moments tells you about how variable how picked and this kind of behaviors So these are all complementary in nature
OK, so I can I can actually cite this here for better understanding.
So you don't understand about this, guys.
So, therefore, what it means is that each one of them is a distribution in itself.
So, each excite is a distribution in itself.
All of you are good with this, guys?
Yes or no?
Yes, Sai Prathesh?
No, I meant to click a thumbs up.
Okay.
Can you give a thumbs up?
Siddharth, Arnav, Raghav,
Shonendu, Sai Prathis.
Shonendu, all good?
Yeah.
Good.
Okay, so what's next?
The next part is understanding that...
So this is basic.
So the next part is understanding
that we have now understood
XI's individually.
So, our time series is nothing but XI's, right?
Individually.
So, we understood XI's individually.
But we have not understood yet
the, is there any relationship between XI's?
Are XI and X, like,
are X1 and X2 related to each other?
Okay.
Did we understand this?
So,
that's important.
Are X1 and X2 related to each other?
So, how to do that?
So I would give that as a homework.
So what you do as a homework is this.
Take a plot take any x i sequence x1 x2 xn just like I have shown here
And then, you plot the xi comma xi plus 1.
Plot it.
And see that, do you find a relationship?
Are they
randomly distributed?
So do you find a relationship?
Do it for multiple stocks.
Then what is a relationship?
What do you see?
Yes, Siddharth.
Is this beat for tomorrow or next week?
Tomorrow.
It will just take
30 minutes of yours.
Yes, Raghav.
Is XI supposed to represent
the close price of the...
You can take any of them.
Okay, and then XI plus 1 would be
the second day or the close price
of the next 5-day interval?
The beginning of the next 5-day?
No, no. So, just like I have done here,
just take the price of any day.
Close price of all the days.
Just take a single NP IRA.
Close price of any day. All the days.
and once you take the close parts of all the day, then you calculate
the first day, second day, second day, third day, third day, fourth day, this pairs
and plot them.
Okay. So, once you plot them, there will be points and then
you will see some relationships. And if you do it for multiple,
you will see more relationships.
So, then based on the relationship,
you tell me
your goal is to tell me
that
what will be your trading strategy
so does it give you trading strategies Also do this for different time points So do this daily okay Take this daily Do this for 5 days 10 days daily let say
like interval equal to daily one day. Let's not go more than that.
And then you vary different period.
That means you can do five days, 15 days, 10 days, six months and see how it evolves.
For different stocks.
yes
so as we
increase the period we will start to see more
of a relationship is that what you're saying
and that's what we need to see
how the relationship builds
yeah how the relationship builds and how
like
is there any
period where
you
are not sure about the trade.
Like whether you should do a trading or not.
There should be some period.
Otherwise, everyone can make money always.
So what are those?
So these are quantitative methods that you find out.
And this will prove you that X, Y and X,
like the pairs are not independent.
They have some relationship, time relationship.
Okay.
This will tell you that.
And yeah, that's it.
And then tomorrow with this, we will be introducing two things.
We'll be introducing three things actually.
I'm just thinking what tomorrow.
Tomorrow actually I will do the research thing because that will be a homework.
And probably I will talk about a bit about Markov chain.
Okay.
you